<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

	<template id="about_us_ept_new" inherit_id="website.aboutus" name="About Us">
		<xpath expr="//div[@id='wrap']" position="replace">
			<div id="wrap">
				<section>
					<div class="container">
						<div class="row s_nb_column_fixed">
							<div class="col-lg-12 s_title" style="text-align: center;padding-top:50px">
								<h4 class="te_s_title_default">
									<img src="/website_template/static/img/hexagon.png" style="width:12px;margin: 0px 12px 22px 0px;"/>
									<font style="font-family: DINNextLTPro-Regular;	font-weight: 600;font-size: 45px;margin-top: 20px;letter-spacing: 3px;display: initial;color: #000;">ABOUT US
									</font>
									<img src="/website_template/static/img/hexagon.png" style="width:12px;margin: 0px 10px 17px 3px;"/>
								</h4>
							</div>
						</div>
					</div>
				</section>
				<section>
					<div class="ab-txt">
						<b>Techlux</b>
						stands for quality made in Switzerland. Our multi-layered products are the epitome
						for perfect design and pure driving pleasure, they represent the successful combination of exclusive
						<b>aesthetics</b>
						and
						<b>dynamic functionality.</b>
						<br/>
						<br/>
						Not only committed car fans come to the
						strong assortment rave about. Techlux is also a permanent point of contact for business customers
						from Switzerland, who make no compromises when it comes to vehicle equipment. Through our
						Comprehensive equipment as well as <b>technological know-how</b> allow us to do it
						The full potential of professional body design. We make it clear that luxury and attractive
						Conditions do not conflict.
						Service puts capital on <b>Techlux</b>.
						<br/>
						<br/>
						Our company is located in the heart of Lucerne, more precisely
						said in Ballwil. We have the experience to innovate every vehicle
						help. Clear lines and imaginative forms cause <b>a sensation.</b> We are known for the love of perfection and distinctive details. Techlux develops contemporary de-luxe bodies,
						whereby modern production processes and <b>selected materials</b> go hand in hand.
						Order processing is uncomplicated and therefore quick - with quick response times
						our customers can count. You have a dedicated contact person at your side at any time, who help with all matters.
					</div>
				</section>
			</div>
		</xpath>
	</template>

</odoo>
